ciim.in 2018-07-23

# Privacy Policy

## CIIM – CHANDIGARH INSTITUTE OF DIGITAL MARKETING

Updated: Sep 11, 2015

**CIIM** respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personal information that you may share with us. This Privacy Policy describes how we may collect and use your personal information. Information We Collect Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, occupation, industry, personal interests, and other information when needed to provide a service or product or carry out a transaction you have requested. Notice – When personal information is collected, **CIIM** will inform you at the point of collection the purpose for the collection. **CIIM**   will not transfer your personal information to third parties.

**Inquiries:** Information collected during the course of You submitting an inquiry via online form, e-mail, fax, or telephone call may be used by **CIIM** to respond to Your inquiries or to contact You to inform You of services of **CIIM** that may be of use to You. Information collected during the course of an inquiry will not be disclosed to any third party.

**Cancellation policy:** **CIIM** follows a transparent and no fuss cancellation policy. Here are the terms of the policy: All Cancellation requests will be considered within 12 hours of course admissions date. **CIIM** will not be held responsible for any third party services, such as job placement, freelancing work, money making, personal business and their own live projects.

**Refund policy:** Due to the nature of its services, **CIIM** does not guarantee any refunds upon cancellation. **CIIM** does not make any guarantees on the basis of job placement, Freelancing work, money making etc. and will not be held responsible for any refund claims thereof.

**Browsing the Website:** Information collected while You’re browsing our website may be used to analyze trends, administer the website, improve site performance, gather broad demographic information, and for security purposes. Such Information will not be disclosed to third parties
